- [ low rumbling ] - [ voices whispering indistinctly ]
[ loud bang ]
[ eerie music ]
[ fly buzzing ]
- [ intense music ] - [ gasps ]
- [ footsteps ] - [ gasps ]
- [ twig shape ] - [ footsteps ]
[ whimpering ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ gasping ]
- Shhh ! Shhh ! - [ girl choking ]
We caught the bitch !
[ shaky breathing ]
[ girl whimpers ]
Please don 't hurt me .
[ woman speaking Welsh ]
[ girl ] Who are you ?
- Somebody please , help me . - [ woman speaking Welsh ]
[ girl ] Please . I just want to go home .
Please . I just want to go home .
[ tense music ]
[ gasps ]
Daddy ?
Daddy , why are you doing this to me ?
- Who are these people ? - [ man ] Look , they 're good people .
They 're - - they 're here to help .
What are you talking about ? Where 's Mom ?
Mommy 's dead , baby . You know that .
You killed her .
- [ girl whimpers ] What ? - You did .
No . Why are you saying these things ? Daddy , please , I just want to go home .
- I just want to go home . - [ speaking Welsh ]
- I 'm so sorry , baby . - Daddy , what is that ?
No ! [ whimpers ]
[ coughs , spits ]
[ tense music ]
Daddy , Daddy , look at me . It 's me .
[ speaking Welsh ]
I just want you to hold me and take me home . Please .
[ dramatic music ]
Please , stop .
I will rip your soul out , Daddy .
[ demonic voice ] I 'll rip your soul out , you pathetic fuck !
Motherfucker , I will kill you like I killed your wife !
[ intense music ]
Fuck !
[ screams ]
[ screaming ]
I love you. baby .
- [ shrieks ] - [ gunshot ]
[ intense music ]
[ mysterious somber music ]
[ insects trilling ]
Hey . How 's it going , Mr. Hot Shit city boy ?
- Hey , Olivia . - Come here .
Two arms , please , like you missed me .
- This is my girl , Natalie . - Oh , the heart breaker from your car shop .
The doctor .
- [ David ] Actually , she 's - - - I 'm a registered nurse .
Nurse , right , sorry . That 's - -
You were supposed to be here two hours ago , man .
And that 's our irresistibly charming Eric .
Teaching high school finally turned you into a bitter old coot , huh ?
No , you did . Kept us waiting here all morning .
Good to see you too , man . Come here .
Look good .
She 's waiting for you in the back .
Great .
[ gentle music ]
[ David ] Hey , Mia .
I 'll be damned .
You actually came .
Come on , I 'm your big brother . Of course I came .
I know I look like roadkill .
You look beautiful , as always .
And you 're a charming liar , as always .
[ dog barks ]
Grandpa ?
Hey . Hey , there , buddy .
We always loved this place , didn 't we ?
He missed you a lot , you know .
- Oh , my God . - What ?
- What is that ? - What ?
Just this right here , what are you ?
[ sighs exasperatedly ] That 's not funny .
This is , uh , it 's made from a buckthorn tree .
It 's supposed to make your will stronger .
But I thought you didn 't believe in that kind of stuff .
I don 't , but you do so , maybe it 'll work .
Okay .
Well then , let 's do this .
Promise me you 'll stay with me until the end .
- I 'm not going anywhere . - Cross your heart .
Okay .
Hope to die .
[ tense music ]
[ Mia ] Okay .
May my friends and family witness this act .
An irrevocable promise to my commitment that ...
Fuck it .
I promise not to touch this shit ever again .
[ ominous music ]
Okay .
Let 's play cold turkey .
[ David ] Hopefully this still works .
Wait .
Looks like someone broke in .
[ Natalie ] Be careful .
What is that smell ?
[ Eric ] Teenagers probably just broke in here to drink beer , bump uglies .
- [ Olivia ] Exactly . - [ flies buzzing ]
Mom would have hated seeing the cabin like this .
[ David ] Okay .
Let 's make this place livable .
[ somber music ]
[ indistinct voices chattering ]
[ David ] Hey .
Are you okay ?
[ Mia ] Do you remember that lullaby Mom used to sing us ?
It was something like ...
" Baby , little baby , it 's time to say goodbye .
- Baby , little baby - - " - Mia , please .
I don 't think you need sad memories in your head right now .
- Mom 's not a sad one . - You know what I mean .
You know in our final days at the hospital ,
Mom sometimes thought I was you .
She even called me David for a whole day once and
- I played along , ' cause ... - Mia , look . I wanted to be there .
Okay ? I did .
By the time Mom got bad , I had just gotten the job at the garage in Chicago .
I don 't know , I had I had a hard time finding the right moment to come back .
And then it was too late , so ...
Maybe you were lucky . Not to see her the way that I did .
[ somber music ]
[ insects trilling ]
- [ nail gun banging ] - [ dog barking ]
[ David ] Looks like she 's doing okay .
David , there 's something you need to know .
Okay .
We already tried this whole thing back in Flint last summer .
Mia made the same promises .
She ... took the same dramatic vow of sobriety
before chucking her dope down the toilet .
She lasted eight hours and quit .
So we don 't want to give her that chance this time .
What do you mean ?
David , when she breaks , and believe me , she will ,
we don 't wanna let her leave .
What do you mean , you wanna force her to stay here ? Mia ?
This time , the only way is the hard way , man .
- She won 't survive another OD . - [ David ] What ?
Mia ODed ?
She didn 't just OD .
Legally , your sister died . They had to defibrillate her .
[ tense music ]
- Jesus . - [ dog barking ]
Look , we all need to be together on this , otherwise it won 't work .
I came here to make things better with my sister , not worse .
If she asks me to take her home at some point , I 'm gonna have to do it .
- [ thunder rumbling ] - [ Mia ] Fuck !
- I can 't stand it ! I can 't stand it ! - [ objects clattering ]
- [ Olivia ] What smell ? What smell ? - [ Mia ] I can 't stand it !
What the fuck is that smell ?
- [ Olivia ] I know , I know . - [ Mia panting ]
I can 't stand that fucking smell anymore !
- [ Olivia ] Lie down , okay ? - [ sobbing ]
[ Olivia ] We 're here for you . I know , I know .
- [ tense music ] - [ Olivia speaking indistinctly ]
We 're all here . We 're all here .
- [ sobbing ] - We 're not going anywhere .
- [ clock ticking ] - [ thunder rumbling ]
[ Olivia ] Withdrawal 's kicking in hard .
This should help you get through the night .
I don 't know what is wrong with you people ,
but there is something dead and it reeks .
- But there 's no smell . - You 're just extra sensitive right now .
[ Mia ] I just can 't stand that fucking smell anymore .
[ dog whining ]
Wait .
[ suspenseful music ]
Oh , is that blood ?
[ music continues ]
- [ flies buzzing ] - [ all groaning ]
[ Mia ] What 's your medical diagnosis now ?
[ Olivia ] It fucking stinks .
[ David ] Shit , careful .
These steps are old and rotten .
[ Eric ] Yeah , like this whole freaking house .
[ David groans ]
Smells like burnt hair .
I think it 's back there .
[ ominous music ]
[ David coughing ]
- [ Eric groans ] - [ David coughs ]
- [ Eric ] Oh my God . - [ flies buzzing ]
[ voices whispering indistinctly ]
- [ David ] What is this ? - I don 't - - I don 't know . Witchcraft ?
[ David ] Who would do this ?
Something burned here .
Look .
[ flies buzzing ]
[ David ] Shit man , what the fuck happened here ?
Let 's not go crazy over this , okay ?
I 'll bury those dead cats out back later .
Yeah .
- Smell 'll be gone in no time . - Yeah , okay .
And what about the voodoo shit they did down there ?
No , no , no , no . Voodoo is more about dolls , personal artifacts .
- This is something different . - Eric . That 's enough .
You shouldn 't have touched anything from that basement .
[ ominous music ]
[ rain pattering ]
[ blade whirring ]
[ ominous music ]
[ voices whispering indistinctly ]
[ music continues ]
[ tense music ]
[ ominous music ]
" Naturom Demon to . " "
[ distorted voice whispering ] Leave this book ...
- He is watching . - [ voice screaming faintly ]
[ distorted voice ] Shatter their bones , they deserve it .
- [ tense music ] - [ Eric inhales sharply ]
[ distorted voice ] Don 't say it , don 't ...
[ music continues ]
" Kunda . "
[ dramatic music ]
- [ pencil scribbling ] - [ ominous music ]
" Astratta . "
[ dramatic music ]
[ rain pattering ]
" Montosse . "
[ intense music ]
[ suspenseful music ]
" Canda . "
- [ screaming ] - [ vomiting , coughing ]
Please , God .
Give me a break .
[ ominous music ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ voices whispering indistinctly ]
- What are you doing ? - I 'm sorry ,
but I have to get out of here right now .
No , come on , slumber party isn 't over yet .
Yeah , we still haven 't played " Fuck , Marry , Kill , " right ?
Mia , please , look , Mia - -
I 'm going insane here . Olivia , I feel like I 'm losing my mind .
- [ David ] Mia , what is it ? - [ Mia gasps ]
I will go through with this , okay ? I just , I can 't do it here .
Mia .
We 've decided we 're not gonna take you back .
[ ominous music ]
[ Eric ] We can 't lose you again .
You 're gonna have to stick it out this time .
David , drive me home .
Come on , David .
Mia .
Maybe they 're right .
You were supposed to be here to support me .
- Not them . - I 'm here for you , Mia ,
- that 's why I can 't - - - [ Mia ] Oh , my God .
I am such an idiot to think for once in my life I could count on you .
[ beads clattering ]
[ Olivia ] Mia , we 're just trying to help you .
[ Mia ] Yeah , well , fuck you very much .
[ door slams ]
Eric , leave her alone .
Mia .
[ rain pattering ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ engine revving ]
Mia !
[ Eric ] Perfect .
Fuck this , fuck , fuck , fuck !
Fuck . Fuck !
[ panting ]
What the fuck am I doing ? What the fuck am I doing ?
- [ intense music ] - [ shrieks ]
[ Mia gasps ]
[ Mia screams ]
[ ominous music ]
[ sighs ]
[ engine sputtering weakly ]
[ music continues ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ ominous music ]
[ David ] Mia !
- [ Olivia ] Mia ! - [ David ] Mia !
- [ dramatic music ] - [ shrieks ]
[ Mia gasping , whimpering ]
[ demonic voice ] Mia !
[ gasps , grunts ]
- [ voices whispering indistinctly ] - [ Mia whimpering ]
[ screams , gasps ]
[ grunting ]
[ whimpering , panting ]
[ screams ]
[ choking ]
[ tense music ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ gasping , whimpering ]
[ demonic voice ] Mia .
[ intense music ]
[ voices whispering indistinctly ]
[ groaning ]
[ tense music ]
[ Mia whimpering ]
[ whimpering , crying ]
[ screaming ]
[ shrieks ]
[ both screaming ]
[ David ] Mia !
[ Olivia ] Mia !
- Mia ! - Mia !
[ ominous music ]
- Mia ! - Shit .
[ Olivia ] Oh , my God .
[ rain pattering ]
Hey , how 's she doing ?
Um , she 's talking about a woman in the woods . How the force attacked her .
I don 't know , it 's just crazy withdrawal talk .
Well , don 't you think we should take her to a hospital ?
I feel like we 're in over our heads here .
Okay , I am giving her the exact same treatment she would get at a hospital .
If we leave now , all of this mess will have been for nothing .
Okay , what about the wounds on her arms ?
I pulled some thorns out .
It looks like she might have run into a thorn bush out there .
She probably did it on purpose .
What ?
David .
From now on , she is gonna do whatever it takes to get out of here .
[ mysterious somber music ]
- Mia . - [ gasps ]
Listen , you gotta get out of those clothes . All right ? Take a shower .
[ whispers ] David .
Please .
You have to get me out of here .
Mia , nobody said this was gonna be easy .
No .
[ whispers ] You don 't understand .
There was something in the woods , David .
[ ominous music ]
And I think it 's in here with us now .
With me in the room ?
[ whimpers ]
Look you know , it 's all in your head .
Just try to get it together .
You 'll feel better tomorrow , okay ? You 'll be glad we were such assholes .
Okay .
[ door shuts ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ voice chittering softly ]
[ intense music ]
[ mysterious somber music ]
Eric , what are you doing ?
Please , would you just get rid of that thing ?
You should be downstairs helping your friend clean up that mess .
I don 't know who you 're talking about .
Come on , don 't act like you don 't care about him . I know you do .
Well , I think we can all agree he hasn 't cared about us
for the past freaking century .
Well , he 's here now .
[ thunder rumbling in distance ]
Yeah .
Truly amazing .
- [ flies buzzing ] - [ David sighs ]
[ grunts ]
[ rain pattering ]
[ ominous music ]
[ David whistling ]
Grandpa .
Grandpa !
- Grandpa . Come here , boy . - [ dog whimpers ]
Fuck .
[ tense music ]
[ grunts ]
Grandpa .
No , no , no .
Hey , boy . Come on , boy .
[ somber music ]
What did you get into ?
Fuck .
What happened ?
[ sniffles ]
[ crying ]
[ ominous music ]
[ shrieking ]
[ tense music ]
- [ David ] Mia ? - [ Natalie ] She 's in the shower .
[ Olivia ] What happened ? David ?
Mia .
Mia , open the door .
[ door rattling ]
[ David ] Mia , open the door .
- Mia , open the door ! - [ Olivia ] David .
[ banging on door ]
[ Olivia ] David , stop ! Tell me what 's going on .
- [ David ] Mia ! Mia , open the fucking door ! - [ banging on door ]
[ tap squeaks ]
[ tense music ]
- [ indistinct arguing ] - [ banging on door ]
- [ steam whistling ] - [ David ] Mia !
- [ David ] Mia , open the fucking door ! - [ Olivia ] David !
- [ banging on door ] - [ David grunting ]
- [ Natalie gasps ] David . - David !
- [ David grunts ] - [ Natalie ] David !
- [ David ] Mia ! - [ dramatic music ]
[ David ] Mia .
Mia !
Olivia !
[ David grunts ]
[ Olivia ] Holy shit !
Mia !
[ dramatic music ]
This is insane .
[ tense music ]
[ panting ]
Fuck , where is it ?
[ dramatic music ]
[ music continues ]
[ engine revving ]
This can 't be happening .
[ water rushing ]
[ wheezing ]
I , um , I ... I gave her a sedative so she should be out for a couple of hours .
But , fuck , her burns are serious . Like , second , third degree .
This is so wrong .
Well , nobody could have known she would do something so twisted .
No , you should have known .
We 've all been following your lead since we got here .
- We should have left when Mia wanted to . - Baby , please .
Okay , let 's not lose our heads . Okay ?
With any luck , it 'll stop raining in a couple of hours ,
and we 'll be able to cross the creek in the morning and take her to a hospital .
Okay ? Everything 's gonna be fine .
" Everything 's gonna be fine " ?
Everything 's gonna be fine .
[ ominous music ]
I don 't know if you 've noticed this , but - - but nothing has been fine .
And everything 's been getting worse every second .
- [ scraping ] - [ gasps ]
[ scraping ]
[ David ] Mia ?
[ bones clicking ]
[ voice chittering softly ]
[ ominous music ]
[ Olivia ] Mia ?
What are you doing ?
[ bones clicking ]
Mia , put the gun down .
Put the gun down , please .
Mia !
- Put the fucking gun down ! - [ gunshot ]
[ high-pitched tone ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ screaming ]
[ demonic voice ] You will die !
[ voice speaks indistinctly ]
One by one we will take you !
[ Mia , distorted voice ] You are all going to die tonight .
- [ tense music ] - [ body thuds ]
Get the gun . The gun , quick !
[ Natalie ] Baby ?
[ Natalie panting , speaking indistinctly ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ chittering ]
- [ Mia hissing ] - [ Olivia screams ]
- [ vomiting ] - [ Olivia gasping ]
[ Olivia screaming ]
- [ thudding ] - [ Olivia gasping ]
Mia !
[ Eric grunts ]
- [ banging ] - [ demonic screaming ]
[ Eric grunting ]
- [ banging ] - [ Mia , distorted ] Let me out !
- She 's totally psychotic . - My God , what happened to her eyes ?
- [ banging ] - [ whimpers ]
[ muffled thudding ]
- What 's she doing ? - [ muffled screaming ]
Sounds like she 's hitting herself against something .
This is impossible .
I just gave her enough sedative to put a horse to sleep .
You can give her another shot .
That could put her into a coma .
For Christ 's sakes , Olivia , she 's gonna kill herself down there .
Go get the shot .
- [ Mia grunts ] - [ thudding ]
I got to get the shrapnel out of my arm .
[ stammers ] I have tweezers in my purse .
David , listen to me .
I - - I - - I don 't think a tranquilizer is gonna do shit .
Because I don 't think we 're dealing with a freaking panic attack here .
I 'm scared that what 's happening to Mia has something to do with
the fucking witchcraft in the basement .
- [ Mia growls ] - [ thudding ]
- [ tense music ] - [ water running ]
[ panting ]
- [ suspenseful music ] - [ demonic shrieking ]
[ screams ]
[ panting ]
- [ ominous music ] - [ paper rustling ]
- [ door creaking ] - [ gasps ]
[ Olivia panting ]
[ ominous music ]
- [ shuddering ] - [ bones clicking ]
[ chittering ]
- [ door slams ] - [ gasps ]
[ Eric ] Olivia ?
[ door opens ]
Olivia ?
[ objects clattering ]
Olivia .
Are you okay ?
[ door creaking ]
[ ominous music ]
Olivia ?
[ water dripping ]
[ flesh squelching ]
[ electricity buzzing ]
Olivia ? What are you doing in there ?
[ flesh squelching ]
Olivia ?
Olivia .
[ suspenseful music ]
Are you okay ?
- [ dramatic music ] - [ choking ]
Oh , my God !
Why the fuck did you do that ?
[ grunts ]
[ groans ]
[ chittering ]
[ Eric shouts ]
[ panting ]
[ Olivia shuddering ]
- [ groaning ] - [ chittering ]
- [ bones cracking ] - [ Eric gasping ]
- [ Eric shouts ] - [ Olivia screaming ]
[ demonic shrieking ]
[ Eric groaning ]
[ Olivia grunting , screaming ]
[ Eric whimpering ]
[ groans ]
[ whimpering ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ growling ]
[ Eric whimpering ]
[ Eric cries out ]
- [ shrieking ] - [ Eric screams ]
[ screaming ]
[ screams ]
[ Eric ] She tried to kill me . She was trying to kill me .
[ dramatic music ]
[ Eric panting ]
[ Eric screams ]
[ rain pattering ]
- [ thunder rumbling ] - [ Eric panting ]
[ Eric panting , whimpering ]
Hold that , you got it ?
[ Eric groans ]
- Hold it there . Okay ? Hold it . - [ Eric whimpering ]
Fuck it .
David .
I did something terrible .
I 'm sure you didn 't mean to hurt her .
That thing I killed was not Olivia .
He 's losing too much blood .
[ David ] Baby , he needs water and sugar . Okay ? Go . Go !
Okay .
- [ David ] All right . - David .
I read a passage from that book
and it was some sort of prayer .
I released something , David .
[ ominous music ]
I released something evil .
[ thunder rumbling ]
- [ banging ] - [ yelps ]
[ panting ]
[ suspenseful music ]
- [ objects clattering ] - [ Mia giggles ]
[ voices whispering indistinctly ]
[ creaking ]
[ door creaking ]
- [ door lock clicks ] - [ panting ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Mia ] Natalie ?
Mia ?
[ Mia whimpering ] Natalie ?
What am I doing down here ?
[ Mia panting , whimpering ]
My leg hurts .
I can 't move .
[ ominous music ]
[ Natalie ] I 'm gonna come down there , okay ?
[ Mia ] Why did you lock me down here ?
[ sobbing ] You were supposed to help me .
Hey , we 're trying to help , okay ?
You were out of control , you know ?
You got violent and we didn 't know what else to do .
Mia .
Look , something really terrible has happened
and we have to get out of here now , okay ?
[ Mia , distorted ] You don 't understand .
He 's not going to let you leave !
And he 's not gonna stop till he has you .
Until he has all of you !
- [ whimpering ] - [ dramatic music ]
[ whimpering , grunting ]
[ panting , yelping ]
[ screaming ]
[ ominous music ]
[ shuddering ]
[ grunts ]
[ suspenseful music ]
- [ Natalie whimpering ] - [ chittering ]
[ panting ]
- [ growling ] - [ Natalie whimpering ]
Please .
[ demonic voice ] I can smell your filthy soul .
[ Natalie screaming ]
[ whimpering ]
[ Natalie whimpering ]
- [ chittering ] - [ Natalie whimpering ]
Kiss me , you dirty cunt !
[ intense music ]
[ Natalie gagging ]
- [ hissing ] - [ Natalie coughing ]
[ whimpering ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ demonic ] Why don 't you come down here so I and suck your cock , pretty boy ?
Mia .
Mia 's not here , you fucking idiot !
Your little sister 's being raped in hell .
[ dramatic music ]
[ Natalie crying ]
I wanna go home .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ David ] Eric .
[ Eric ] I don 't know why , but I thought this would end it .
But this book does not burn .
It does not fucking burn .
Tell me what 's going on here .
[ ominous music ]
- [ tense music ] - [ gasping ]
[ voices whispering indistinctly ]
[ Eric ] This book uses some ...
ancient alphabet , there 's some translations , but just scattered notes .
They all refer to some ...
evil entity , uh , the Taker of Souls .
Demon .
It says ...
" Once he feasts on five souls ,
the sky will bleed again and the abomination will rise from hell . "
[ Natalie groans ]
[ groans , pants ]
[ ominous music ]
[ grunting ]
[ groans ]
This is insane .
This thing is attached to Mia 's soul like a leech .
It 's becoming her .
If we want to stop this , if we want to help Mia ...
[ ominous music ]
[ voice whispering ] Kill her .
... I think we 're gonna have to kill her .
- What did you say ? - It - - everything say - -
Eric ! We 're not gonna fucking kill anybody !
Are you listening to yourself ?
What about those dead cats down in the basement ?
I mean , maybe they had some disease . I mean , some virus that it spread to Mia
and then she - - she passed it to Olivia when she puked all over her face .
What kind of a virus makes a person cut off their face with a piece of glass ?
[ groaning ]
Oh , God . Oh , God . [ whimpers ]
[ chittering ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ whimpers ]
[ dramatic music ]
- [ door slams ] - [ shouts ]
I don 't know what we 're dealing with here , okay ?
But it stopped raining and in a couple hours , the river will be clear .
And we 're gonna get out of this place . All of us .
It doesn 't matter where we go .
If we don 't do something right now , we 're all gonna be dead by then !
- [ dramatic music ] - [ squelching ]
[ grunting , whimpering ]
[ door creaking ]
[ chittering ]
[ choking ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ growling ]
[ gasping ]
Don 't do it , you little bitch , don 't cut it off !
[ whirring ]
[ suspenseful music ]
- [ demon ] Don 't cut it off . - Fuck you .
[ whirring ]
No ! No ! No ! No ! No ! No ! No ! No !
[ demon speaking indistinctly ]
- [ bone snaps ] - [ screaming ]
- [ electricity sparking ] - [ dramatic music ]
[ suspenseful music ]
I had to do it . [ whimpering ]
And I feel much better now .
[ Natalie panting ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ giggling ]
[ David ] Hold on , baby , hold on , please .
Okay , Eric and I , we 're gonna ... we 're gonna put a stop to this , okay ?
I promise that everything 's going to be fine , okay ? Okay .
She just cut her fucking arm off . Does that sound fine ?
[ mysterious somber music ]
These inscriptions are confusing ,
sometimes contradictory , they 're consistent about one thing .
In order to stop this , the possessed must be cleansed .
Purified .
The book describes three specific ways .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Eric ] A live burial .
[ voice whispering ] Live burial .
Bodily dismemberment .
[ voice whispers ] Bodily dismemberment .
And purification by fire .
[ woman speaking Welsh echoing ]
You sure this 'll work ?
If we ...
[ mysterious somber music ]
If I kill my sister ...
she 'll be at peace ?
Am I ... am I sure ? Of course not , this is not a science book .
Look , I 'm sure of one thing .
Whatever is inside Mia is the cause of all this .
If she dies , then this thing is going to die with her .
[ David ] What if she just lost her mind ?
What if she just needs a doctor ?
What ? A doctor ?
My mom died in a mental hospital . She was crazy .
She was deranged , she was a monster .
I 've always feared that me and Mia would end up like her .
[ laughing weakly ]
So you 're just a fucking coward .
You know exactly what we have to do , but you 're too scared to go through with it .
I 'm gonna burn this fucking place down .
I 'm gonna end this nightmare .
Why don 't you just run away ?
Go hide beneath some rock somewhere .
You know , you 're great at that .
[ chittering ]
- [ nail gun fires ] - [ grunts , choking ]
- [ nail gun fires ] - [ Natalie choking ]
[ nail gun fires ]
[ Eric ] Oh , shit .
[ chittering ]
- [ tense music ] - [ bones clicking ]
- [ nail gun firing ] - [ Eric screaming ]
[ David shouts ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ nail gun firing ]
[ shrieking , hissing ]
- [ voices whispering indistinctly ] - [ nail gun firing ]
- [ David yelps ] - [ Eric whimpering ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ nail gun firing ]
- [ Eric whimpering ] - [ bones clicking ]
[ demon chittering ]
- [ nail gun firing ] - [ Eric screaming ]
- [ screams ] - [ nail gun firing ]
[ Eric screaming ]
[ sobs ]
- [ David shouts ] - [ thudding ]
- [ grunts ] - [ Eric hyperventilating ]
[ tense music ]
[ grunting , groaning ]
[ groaning ]
Where the fuck did she go ?
[ whimpering ]
Take it before she does .
[ ominous music ]
[ metal scraping ]
[ David grunting ]
[ shrieking ]
[ nail gun firing ]
[ dramatic music ]
- [ Eric whimpering ] - [ chittering ]
[ hyperventilating ]
[ Eric groaning ]
- Stop ! - [ nail gun firing ]
[ intense music ]
- [ Eric panting , grunting ] - [ nail gun firing ]
[ nail gun clicking ]
- No ! No ! No ! - [ chittering ]
No ! No ! No , no , no !
[ screaming ]
[ groaning , sobbing ]
[ shotgun blasts ]
- [ panting ] - [ blood dripping ]
David .
[ mysterious somber music ]
[ sobbing ]
Why are you hurting me ?
My face hurts . [ sobs ]
Why ? Why ?
Why does my face hurt ? [ sobbing ]
- [ Natalie choking ] - [ whispering ] Baby , baby ...
[ Natalie stops choking ]
[ somber music ]
[ crying ] Natalie ...
[ Eric laughs darkly ]
[ ominous music ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Come on . Come on , man , here we are .
- [ thunder rumbling ] - [ Eric groans ]
Hey , hey , hey . Hold on . Don 't die on me , please .
Dying wouldn 't be so bad right now .
I just don 't want to become the devil 's bitch .
[ ominous music ]
I 'm gonna do what I gotta do .
I 'm gonna do what I gotta do , okay ?
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ mysterious somber music ]
[ gasoline dripping ]
Sorry , Mia .
I love you .
[ Mia ] ♪ Baby , little baby ♪
♪ It 's time to say goodbye ♪
♪ Baby , little baby ♪
- ♪ I 'll miss you day and night ♪ - [ faint voices laughing ]
[ Mia ] ♪ Baby , my sweet baby ♪
♪ I 'll write you every day ♪
- [ David mouthing words ] - [ Mia ] ♪ Baby , don 't cry , baby ♪
♪ I wish that I could stay ♪
[ ominous music ]
I can 't do this .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ lightning crackling ]
[ dramatic music ]
- [ electricity sparking ] - [ machine whirring ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
Okay .
This time , the only fucking way is the hard way .
- [ chains rattling ] - [ lock clicks ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ man 's voice whispering ] David .
[ woman 's voice whispering ] Murderer .
[ man 's voice whispering ] Coward .
- [ banging ] - [ wood creaking ]
- [ objects clattering ] - [ tense music ]
[ door slams ]
[ voices whispering indistinctly ]
[ water sloshing ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ demon roaring , shrieking ]
- [ David screams ] - [ demon snarling ]
[ David shouts ]
[ shrieking ]
[ David shouting ]
[ shrieking , growling ]
[ demon shrieking ]
[ tense music ]
[ muffled yelling ]
[ demon shrieks ]
[ coughing ]
[ ominous music ]
[ David ] Eric .
[ Eric grunts ]
[ somber music ]
[ David coughs ]
[ Eric coughing ]
[ grunts ]
- Hey . Hey . - [ wheezing ]
David .
I missed you , man .
- Yeah . - [ wheezing ]
You know that , buddy . [ wheezing ]
[ music continues ]
[ ominous music ]
[ dramatic music ]
- [ thunder rumbling ] - [ shovel scraping ]
[ David panting ]
- David ? - [ thunder rumbling ]
[ Mia ] David ?
I can 't move .
I can 't breathe . David !
[ panting ] Help me !
[ screaming ] Help me , David !
- You 're not her . - [ Mia ] David !
- [ thundering rumbling ] - [ screaming ]
[ David ] You 're not her !
Why do you hate me , David ?
[ mysterious somber music ]
I know you do .
You left home .
[ distorted ] You left me all alone with our sick mother .
And I was just a kid .
You made me lie .
[ thunder rumbles ]
Every time she screamed your name , I told her you were coming to see her .
Like you promised .
But you never did .
Please stop it . I 'm begging you .
I know Mother hates you now .
And she waits for you in hell .
[ thunder rumbles ]
[ laughing darkly ]
Shut up . Shut up .
[ thunder rumbles ]
[ demon panting ]
[ sobs ]
- [ heartbeat thumping ] - I 'm so sorry .
I should have been there .
I should have been there for you .
[ heartbeat stops ]
[ mysterious somber music ]
[ grunting ]
[ music continues ]
[ electricity zaps ]
[ whirring ]
[ electricity crackles ]
Come on . Please , come back .
[ whirring ]
[ electricity crackles ]
Come on , come on , come on .
Come on , Mia , come back to me , come on , please .
[ electricity crackling ]
[ whirring weakly ]
[ melancholic music ]
Okay , you 're at peace .
You 're at peace now .
[ music continues ]
[ Mia ] David ?
Mia ?
[ emotional music ]
[ Mia crying ]
It was so horrible .
[ David ] It 's okay . It 's all over now .
Thanks for not leaving me , David .
Wait here . I 'm gonna get the car keys .
- Okay ? - Yeah .
[ somber music ]
[ chittering ]
[ dramatic music ]
- [ bones cracking ] - [ David choking ]
[ David grunts ]
[ coughing ]
[ intense music ]
- David ? ? [ gasping ] - Go !
- Please , no , no , no , no . - Go . Go !
I 'm not gonna go anywhere . I 'm not going anywhere !
- [ gasps ] - [ chittering ]
[ dramatic music ]
Mia , take the keys . Look at me . Let 's go .
Come on , come on , let 's go .
Get outta here .
[ Mia screaming ] No !
No ! David !
- [ chittering ] - [ banging on door ]
[ muffled screaming ]
[ Mia ] David ! David !
[ demonic voice ] He 's coming .
[ gunshot ]
[ flames roaring ]
[ Mia gasping ]
[ explosion ]
[ muffled voices screaming ]
[ sobs ]
[ mysterious somber music ]
[ ominous music ]
[ blood splats ]
[ rain pattering ]
- [ intense music ] - [ screaming ]
[ demon growling ]
[ roaring ]
[ gasping ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ Mia panting ]
- [ keys jingling ] - Shit . [ panting ]
- [ roaring ] - [ screaming ]
[ sizzling ]
[ screaming ]
[ intense music ]
[ panting , whimpering ]
Mia .
- [ panting , whimpering ] - [ dramatic music ]
[ engine sputtering ]
[ intense music ]
Come here , bitch !
[ demon snarling ]
[ tense music ]
[ engine sputtering ]
[ demon shrieks ]
[ screaming ]
[ Mia grunts ]
[ intense music ]
- [ engine sputtering ] - [ chittering ]
[ chittering ]
[ growling ]
- [ grunting ] - [ engine sputtering ]
Come on .
[ engine starting ]
- [ chainsaw revving ] - [ demon screaming ]
[ demon shrieking ]
[ metal creaking ]
[ screaming ]
[ intense music ]
[ continues screaming ]
[ growling ]
[ Mia sobbing ]
[ engine rumbling ]
[ Mia grunting ]
You 're gonna die here , you pathetic junkie .
I 've had enough of this shit .
[ Mia grunting ]
[ Mia screaming ]
[ screaming ]
[ intense music ]
I will feast on your soul .
Feast on this , motherfucker .
- [ chainsaw revving ] - [ intense music ]
Die !
[ demon screeching ]
[ dark music ]
Go back to hell , bitch .
[ faint distorted voices screaming ]
[ somber music ]
[ emotional music ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ ominous music ]
[ intense music ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ music continues ]
[ intense music ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ music continues ]
[ mysterious somber music ]
[ man ] I believe I have made a significant find in the Candarian Ruins ,
a volume of ancient Sumerian burial practices and funerary incantations .
It is entitled Naturom Demon to . Roughly translated , Book of the Dead .
The book is bound in human flesh and inked in human blood .
It deals with demons , demon resurrection ,
and those forces which roam the forest and dark bowers of man 's domain .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ man ] The first few pages warned that these enduring creatures
may lie dormant , but are never truly dead .
They may be recalled to active life
through the incantations presented in this book .
It is through recitation of these passages
that the demons are given license to possess the living .
[ music continues ]
[ man ] I have seen the dark shadows moving in the woods and I have no doubt
that whatever I have resurrected through this book is sure to come calling for me .
[ fly buzzing ]
[ ominous music ]
Groovy .